1staudiovisual.co.uk 2012-06-25

# Privacy Policies : 1staudiovisual UK

| 

**_M.A.  ,Says :_**

Last Monday I searched local shops and the net to find a retailer who could supply a certain make of washing machine. However, no one could deliver within a week and all quoted delivery charges. Then I saw the machine on your web site and ordered it. We received a phone call from you that same day and the goods arrived the next day. You also took my old machine away without quibble or charge. Excellent service!!! I shall certainly recommend you to my friends.

**_Craig Sellar  ,Says :_**

Hi Paul, the Samsung arrived yesterday afternoon. Unboxed, up on it's stand, and looks great after a few picture setting tweaks. Over the moon with it. Great service, cheers again for the help. Craig.

**_Cecil Wyn Davies  ,Says :_**

I have recived my TV.Tthanks for the quick delivery. The goods was in good order. Thanks again. C W Davies.

**_John Jones  ,Says :_**

Ordered 42" Led TV 8am Thur, delivered to North Wales by 09.30 Fri. Will certainly use again.

**_Roger Bainbridge  ,Says :_**

Order number 154538 safely delivered this morning - connected and working well. Many thanks for prompt service at reasonable price. Regards, Roger Bainbridge.

**_Mark Simpson  ,Says :_**

Fantastic! ...lol I'm soooooo in love with the TV, the deal and the customer service, should I need any more tech, I'll be checking in here first! (Guys! ...it seems to have arrived before you shipped it! MIRACULOUS! ...LOL)

**_Barry  ,Says :_**

Service as it should be.

**_Charles Aghabi  ,Says :_**

TV received on Friday 27th April. Thank you for an excellent deal and very quick free delivery (2 days!). We're very pleased with our purchase!

**_Rosemarie  ,Says :_**

I needed a copy of the original invoice for a query with the manufacturer. 1staudiovisual were able to provide this for me promptly. Thank-you! Excellent service and I recommend you.

**_Edward Lettis  ,Says :_**

Hi Paul, Order no 153942 The TV has arrived safely and in good order. It is now up and running and and we have been very impressed by the excellent service provided by you and the courier. We were very well informed throughout the process and I will not hesitate to use you again, and to recommend the company to others. Regards and thank you again, Edward Lettis.

|  |  |  |   |   
---|---|---  
  | 

We will treat all your Personal Information as confidential (although we reserve the right to disclose this information in the circumstances set out below). We will keep it on a secure server and we will fully comply with all applicable UK Data Protection and consumer legislation. 

When you shop on this website, we will ask you to input and will collect Personal Information from you such as your name, e-mail address, billing address, delivery address, telephone number, product selections, credit card or other payment information and a password. We may also collect information about where you are on the internet (eg the URL you came from, IP address, domain types like .co.uk and .com), your browser type, the country and telephone area code where your computer is located, the pages of our website that were viewed during your visit, the advertisements you clicked on, and any search terms that you entered on our website ("User Information"). We may collect this information even if you do not register with us. 

You should be aware that this site is being monitored and may capture information about your visit that will help us improve the quality of our service. 

We confirm that any Personal Information which you provide to us (or which is available on public registers) and any User Information from which we can identify you, is held in accordance with the registration we have with the Data Commissioner's Office. We use your information only for the following purposes:

  * Processing your orders; 

  * To maintain guarantee records and any after sales service, which may require us to pass your details to the organisation carrying out such service.

  * For statistical or survey purposes to improve this Website and its services to you; 

  * To serve website content and advertisements to you; 

  * To administer this website; 

  * If you consent, to notify you of products or special offers that may be of interest to you. 

You agree that you do not object to us contacting you for any of the above purposes whether by telephone, e-mail or in writing and you confirm that you do not and will not consider any of the above as being a breach of any of your rights under the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003. 

If you are purchasing a television or television receiving equipment from us, please note that the Wireless Telegraphy Act 1967 requires us to notify the TV Licensing Authority, giving full details of the address to which the TV will be delivered. This is in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and other applicable laws. When you create a shopping account while ordering online you will be given the option to receive information from 1staudiovisual by e-mail about products, promotions or special offers which we feel may be of interest to you. In the event that you do not wish to be contacted for such purposes, ensure that you tick the appropriate box as you go through the registration process. You may unsubscribe from our contact list at any time by visiting our website and clicking on Contact Us and making your request. 

Your Personal Information may be disclosed to reputable third parties who will help process your order or provide after-sales service. 1staudiovisual requires all such third parties to treat your personal information as fully confidential and to fully comply with all applicable UK Data Protection and consumer legislation from time to time in place. 

You should be aware that if we are requested by the police or any other regulatory or government authority investigating suspected illegal activities to provide your Personal Information and /or User Information, we are entitled do so.   
When entering any of our contests or prize draws, you provide your name, email address and mailing address. If you win, we will send the prize to the address entered and notify you by email. When you enter a contest or prize draw, you are also included in our newsletter list to receive notice of promotions, specials and new additions to the Website. You may unsubscribe from this news list by following the unsubscribe instructions in any email received. 

We use Cookies to keep track of your current shopping session to personalise your experience and so that you may retrieve your shopping basket at any time.

|    
|   |   
|   
---  

CUSTOMER SERVICE

    ◊ 

    ◊ [Customer Support](http://www.1staudiovisual.co.uk/catalog/order_support.php)  

| 

SHOPPING HELP

    ◊ 

    ◊ [Privacy Policy](http://www.1staudiovisual.co.uk/catalog/privacy.php)  
    ◊ [Terms & Conditions](http://www.1staudiovisual.co.uk/catalog/conditions.php)  
    ◊ [Customers Comment](http://www.1staudiovisual.co.uk/catalog/comments.php)  

| 

MY ACCOUNT

    ◊ 

    ◊ [My Account](https://www.1staudiovisual.co.uk/catalog/account.php)  

| 

COMPANY INFO

    ◊ 

    ◊ [Careers](http://www.1staudiovisual.co.uk/catalog/jobs.php)  

| 

TOOLS & RESOURCES

    ◊ 

    ◊ [Sitemap](http://www.1staudiovisual.co.uk/catalog/sitemap.php)  
    ◊ [Affliates](http://www.1staudiovisual.co.uk/catalog/affiliate_info.php)  

---|---|---|---|---
